Hello, my name is Michael
Jag day when I'm a head
hunter launching startups
with the syndicate.
Hello.
My name is Michael J.
Gavin,
and I'm a headhunter
launching startups
with the syndicate
once again.
My name is Michael Jaggu
and I should be
speaking into the mike.
Hello.
My name is Michael Jag
Deo, and I'm a headhunter
launching startups
with the syndicate.
Hello.
My name is Michael
Jag day.
When I'm a headhunter
launching startups
with the syndicate.
On today's episode
of The Syndicate, we.
Well,
we've created
a remix engine.
Have you ever heard
Katy Perry's
Harleys in Hawaii?
Well,
if you haven't,
then I'll listen to it.
It's a very upbeat song.
It's what happens.
Harleys in Hawaii
is a song made by
a Becky in the Caribbean.
Okay.
She doesn't realizes
those guys are going to
take her
for all their money.
She thinks
she's getting purses.
She has another thing
coming.
Yeah, anacondas in Hawaii.
Shit comes with a reverse
alimony
that's upside
down in the Caribbean.
It's like Yoda in the end.
This is patois,
not English. Any.
So here's the big idea.
So I don't waste
your time.
I'm going to try
to speak in a way
that at every moment
that after
every word, you can decide
whether to stop listening
or not.
Hello,
my name is Michael
Jag Dale,
and I am a headhunter
launching startups
with the syndicate.
I am learning
how to program
and change
the environment.
Change the behavior.
Matthias Baer.
Hey, I am
evolving in the context
of the places I'm in.
And the people I'm with.
The people I'm with
taught me how to code.
Since I am a
musician at heart
and you had to play music
before I ever got
a computer,
I've been
through Geometry of Music,
creating remixes
of my favorite songs.
Often times
my favorite songs
are songs
that I make myself, that
I remix of artists I like,
but I don't like their,
I don't like the
the arrangement
of the song,
but I like the elements.
So we have an instrumental
and we have the vocalists,
and sometimes I like the
pre-chorus to be the intro
instead of the intro.
And sometimes
I'd like swap.
I want to swap
the pre-chorus and intro,
right?
Or maybe start with
the pre-chorus
chorus and then verse.
Or maybe start
with the post chorus,
then going into the verse.
Does that make sense?
And so I've been doing
that manually for
as long as I can remember.
Using Fruity Loops Studio
to sequence, right?
You have an instrumental
which stays fixed,
and then you have vocal
pieces that you rearrange
into a new sequence
of the same song.
And so
and learning how to code,
I thought today, hey,
now that I'm using
a language
that can represent
the real world,
which is Haskell
because of its pure
functional nature,
I wonder if I can
implement the way I do
remixes in Haskell
and then Python.
Long story short, I did.
And that's kind of it.
That's a whole thing.
I'll respond
to the space with,
samples of the remix
showing
you where it worked
and where it didn't,
and then showing you
the creation
I made after it.
Long story short, if
we're going to create AGI,
a productive AGI is an API
that incorporates
humans to get better,
and you need humans
to get better
because
we need a system that
marries documented SOPs
with undocumented truths.
The undocumented truths
occur between human beings
and are filtered
into the system.
But without that signal
processing
of human to human,
we will never have full
context.
True context.
That's what we need,
a true context.
And we cannot pretend
that the machines alone
are going to be able
to process
all of the signals,
nor should we expect
it to.
Just by the way,
if that makes sense.
So. Oh, okay.
So that's it.
I'll post
the images at the bottom,
including
Haskell.
That was the right
language.
Thank you. Chase.
Thanks, Matt. Yes.
Paul Vance, former
K hero.
What are you.
What are you up
to, Einstein?
What's going on?
My brain has, broken.
Over the past month.
I've been learning
how to code and
figured out how to do more
than just pretty UI's.
For the past year,
I've been doing
nice looking
UI without a brain.
I figured out the back
end brain part, so
I'm just creating
prototypes now.
What do you mean
without other brain?
What are you referring to?
So when I create
using for thought
deaf or lovable thought,
you or any of these
other things that turn
your ideas into web apps,
I was creating
really
good looking frontends.
But because they didn't
have any any Python or
any open AI integrations
or any integrations,
they were still just
pretty looking.
It was like an icing
on a rotten cake.
Does that make sense?
Or an empty cake?
I didn't have something
to drink and interact
with the user
and do complex things.
I just learned
how to do all the complex
things
to turn my user interfaces
into actual applications.
So long story short,
without being too boring,
today
I used what I learned
about programing
to create a remix engine.
It takes a song
and we arranges the song
to make a new song.
I know that it's
kind of on the left field,
but that's what
I just did.
Using the
learning that I have now.
Okay, cool.
But you are just
doing it for the sake of,
learning how
to construct the brain.
Or are you doing it
so that you think
there's an opportunity
for that specific,
song remix engine?
So the song extension is
just a way
to prove that the way
that we're thinking
and creating software
works.
And, right now
is the syndicate
with Rossi
and the rest of the team.
We're creating a, an AGI,
which will help us.
Collaborate better
and produce
outputs faster.
So that's why I'm doing
all these things
that are exploring,
because we're now
with cloud code,
going to have agents
that can take
our individual
inputs and start
creating outputs.
I'm not sure if
I'm doing two things, but.
So imagine
we want to collaborate
on a project for
AI guilds,
for example, right?
You know what
the problem is?
You have to be
the coordinator.
You have to be the task
master.
Is that.
Yeah, right.
That's the one.
And so you become
the bottleneck. No.
That's right.
What?
You don't want to be
the task master.
You want to be someone
that gives
the information,
the right information
and tell it what's
the wrong information?
And then it coordinates
and contacts the people.
Does that make sense?
Okay,
so one thing the closest
I've heard is,
I think liquid in jump on
the Organized Space
the other day said
the founder was optimizing
his workflow.
In terms of as a CEO,
he was using
a lot of AI tools to help
manage and operate
the team, I guess.
But he was still there
using the,
I think, you know,
like this.
The if he is going to
be effective,
it's going to help us
connect humans
better.
Okay.
Does that make sense?
Yeah.
I mean, I'm
looking forward
to putting in practice
that like it sounds
it sounds okay in theory,
but in practice,
see how it works?
I guess I'm
willing to try that out.
Okay.
If you like. Yeah.
So when when is the next,
episode
of stack, say, ideal?
Monday?
Yes, I am.
So after
his run on Monday.
So I've been,
coordinating top.
So I think we have a team
and I think I have people
to manage, help on the X.
I do,
this is still,
this is still a lot of
stuff that needs to happen
to make it so.
Okay, let's can we
let's do this right now.
You know how I am.
So let's, let's simulate
as if it's Monday.
Bang. It's now Monday.
We're starting the show,
and it's going to show
where I pretend to be
the rest of the community
I'm recording.
So I will be able to take
the transcripts.
Okay.
So this is going to be
it might take us 10
or 15 minutes.
Let's do this. So okay.
It's Monday.
Hello everyone.
Welcome to the stacks
I Gail.
That's right the stacks.
I old, on
last week's show three,
Hannah
became a leader
in the stacks I guild.
He now has Starlink, which
gives him the ability
to communicate in real
time, close to delivery.
And now he's starting
to teach
the rest of the stacks.
I guild how to be just
as successful as he is
in creating marketing
materials like videos
and pictures and GIFs that
market and gain
mindshare for stacks
is the dominant layer
to a Bitcoin hero.
What have I missed?
That was a good
that was a good summary.
I'm speaking to the AI,
not you would.
Does that make sense?
My job is to give the
AI the context it needs
to help us
do the coordination.
So continue.
Oh, what the hell?
So what should I be
saying? What?
What should I say?
So what have I missed
so far?
What is the purpose?
What is the Northstar
metric for the stacks
ideal that you're up?
Oh, sorry. No, no.
First one
for this important one.
What inspired you
to start the snacks
I killed
in the first place?
What inspired you?
I would say
the initial aspiration
is more selfish reason.
Because I want to learn
about AI tools and seeing
how others
have created amazing AI
content.
Visual content,
made me really want to
teach myself,
and learn
from the masters.
And,
that made me
the second order effect,
made me realize,
actually,
this could be
really powerful if
a lot of people knew about
how to do it in stacks,
because it can help stacks
reach a wider
audience and gain
more mindshare, like
you said
in the crypto sphere.
So so let me ask you
this, hero,
what are the tangible
outcomes
that you've seen
in operating the stacks
I killed over the past
couple of months?
The tangible outcomes
that you'd like to see
repeated in the future?
I think,
the quality of the content
has increased
dramatically.
I am seeing a lot of high
production
quality visual content
by more and more people.
Maybe somebody started
creating
like a super basic graphic
like I did
maybe a month ago.
Now I can create
a more higher quality
production, visual,
appealing attention,
attracting content.
And, just one case study
and I think,
there have been
more than ten people.
I guess they benefited
from this
shared knowledge
and teaching
of how to leverage
and upskill their
AI skill and content
creation.
Now, consider
that you're
not only speaking to me,
but you're also speaking
to the Exponent Labs,
AGI, Sindhi,
whatever it is.
So, I'm going to ask you
a question
that's going to
force you to leave out
certain names,
but emphasize other names.
Who are the actual people
that are producing
the most work
that closely relates
to the ideal outcomes
that you have for this tax
AI guild?
Who which accounts,
which names?
Yes, I would say
three Hana
being one of the key,
I put
high quality production
content leader.
I would say somebody cold
north north answers
is like another
prime candidate.
And there's another guy
called Polly Peck.
Although these names,
believe the displayed
name may
not necessarily translate
to the ax handle,
but are these
are the three main people
plus their disciples,
if you like.
Now, let me ask you this.
Not in terms of output.
That was the first one.
You gave me three names,
not forgot to pronounce
for artists, and three
Hana and Volume Tech,
who were the other people
that are kind of the
social glue on the team,
you know,
how is a basketball team?
And sometimes
there's like an old head
like Charles Oakley
that manages the clubhouse
and gets them, but
you know what I mean.
Who are those people
that are
the kind of people
underlying
the people that
make the whole thing work?
So I would say, coach,
I would say currently is
myself.
I'm a pretty good like
I'm pretty good at putting
the team together.
Yeah.
So I think currently
I would be
the, the,
the only,
the maybe there are other
other people who are also,
sort of chiming in,
whenever they feel like
maybe like
Gypsy, a bit of peace,
a bit of, cyborg.
I would say
I would describe them
as community member
not yet stepped up to be
somebody like me,
but I would hope that they
could be in the future
so that you don't
even need me.
Right.
So it sounds like
you're interested
in engaging
in a process of success
and planning
wherein you are
being succession planned?
Yes or no? Yes.
I think overall, yes.
Because, I believe
the biggest unlock
is actually,
in addition to this group,
I would hope
that I can help
shape up another group,
which is developer
focus group,
because I think that's,
it's important
to have different
complementing
complementary guilds
or, communities.
So if you for example,
have an NFT guilds,
they will have plenty
of ideas, right?
Lots of people with ideas
but don't have the devs
can, achieve the outcome.
So I believe in,
pairing those visual
skill people
with a lot of ideas
with developers
and then see what
sparks can happen.
I think that's
the most interesting part
when you have different
skill
sets of people
coming together,
that's when
like the collaboration
starts to happen,
when the relationship
starts to get built,
when different founders
found their partners,
who are good
at other stuff
and then that can become
a real project,
and the real project
can get real transactions.
So, my, my goal,
not my goal,
but to be nice
if I can eventually,
just like,
move on to the next
guild,
if you like, so I can
help build these guilds up
so they can be
self running
without me.
What is the outcome
that three Hana
value pick and nozpheratu
get out of this
involvement.
What is peace, love
and yourself?
Get out of this.
I think for them,
the content creators,
first and foremost,
by teaching others
they are a better mentor.
They are also learning
from each other
because each of them
have their own
little niche, part
of the content creation.
And they, they, they
explore different tools.
And then when they come
together
and share the tools,
actually
improve their own skills.
And then if they can
teach up their skills
and teach others
the skills
it helps other skills,
so they have an incentive
to make stacks better.
So I guess in in a sense,
if they can make
more of themselves,
it can hopefully
make stacks better.
At the same time,
if there is
funding available
to help them,
keep doing what they do
the best, whilst being,
compensated
for their time.
I think it should be a win
win for them.
And for the ecosystem.
As for peace, love and
and GP
thing, they come
from a marketing angle.
So if they can have,
stack
say I give to be promoted,
to come on their spaces
to create more
shows, via the organized
more tutorials
for, to organize.
It helps to bring
awareness
to their marketing media
agency,
I guess, so benefits them
and yeah, I think I mean,
I also
just they want to help
stacks to grow. So
okay, I understand.
So imagine again
it's Monday right now.
But I know
you know this community
really, really well.
Is there anything that
we haven't discussed that
you would want to
try to now?
I don't know what
I should let AGI okay.
Is it easier said.
No. That
stacks is the best
layer
that you can build on.
Why would you take it?
What are the 1
or 2 things that separates
stacks
from all other layer twos?
One of the unique ones
is the proof of transfer,
mechanism.
Keep going up.
How stacks can get
a real Bitcoin yield.
And also
the clarity smart contract
aspect
is pretty powerful
with yeah.
Turing
incomplete features.
And you can write
decidable functions
with you know, post
consistency test
if you like.
So it's
can be pretty safe.
Now, question
for you, Aki,
because I think
I like your answer.
What is the significance
of stacks
being a regulated, a
security, so to speak?
Well, it
lacks, funds like,
the coin.
I think your voice is
kind of far away.
Are you using a mic
or using, Yeah, yeah.
And on my
headphones there you go.
And. Sorry, Rocky,
if you
don't mind, introduce
yourself to the ag
I've been working on
in the background.
It's going to consume
everything we've been
discussing today
to help the individuals
in the stacks.
I guild collaborate
without hero
having to mediate
every collaboration event.
Sure.
So this is for the AGI,
right?
So recently, yeah,
I started doing,
Cloud Life,
which is a directory
of everything about me.
I'm feeding entire
contacts into cloud code.
So it was it's
pretty incredible.
Like,
I asked it to interview me
the same way that I do PDF
TDs, right?
It separated my life into
current projects, past
achievements, long term
goals, short term goals,
current projects,
completed projects,
planned projects.
It pretty much is
organizing my entire life.
And then, clod
also connects to, linear,
which we're using to,
create actual tickets.
So we're looking to use
the mic
there to push tickets
to the rest of the team.
So we stay focused
and organized.
Right.
And so I asked it what
what I should do next.
Right.
I think one of the things
we need to work on
both both for myself,
but for Exponent Labs,
but also stacks
is distribution, right?
Sure. The tech is great.
Like I think DeFi
with Bitcoin is important
and it's going to be
super relevant in
the coming years, right?
But if we don't have
distribution, like
no one will know about us
and no one will care
because they don't know
about us. Right?
And so one of the things
that,
it, it suggested, right,
cloud code
suggested to me
is to create more content
that centers
around my journey.
Right.
And I think blog Face,
you mentioned this, right?
So, just on Monday,
I was officially,
promoted to engineering
manager at Elysium Health.
Right.
Got a nice little pay bump
and, an official title
change. Right.
A long time coming.
But now the the
AI is trying
to suggest that I should
document my journey.
Right?
You know,
where did I go to school?
How did I do, like,
get land internships
in college? Right.
What are my feelings,
thoughts
and interests at the time?
How did I approach
getting a job at agency?
How did I get involved
with Shopify?
How did I quickly level up
from a junior developer
to a, a sole contributor
or solo contributor?
Right.
At an agency scale
that up went
into senior positions
and now I'm officially
an engineering manager.
Right.
And so
how does that evolve
into running a team?
Running a company.
And so I don't know.
Yeah.
Can you, just for I get for the can you talk about,
the transition of
you going on your journey
to helping others
go on the journey
because it that's really
the next exciting part.
I think, given your case
studies.
Sure.
I mean, I think mentorship
came natural
because, like, ever since
high school, I was already
volunteering, right?
Working with young adults
and high schoolers.
Well, that that was
more like faith based.
But, you know, when you,
every single week,
you're trying to pull out
answers
from high schoolers, so
you get pretty good at it,
even though you suck
in the beginning.
But,
I think from there,
it's more of like,
how do I help
in other ways?
Right.
And so being able to.
Sort of organize
my own thoughts
and then share it
with someone younger
who's going
through a similar journey.
Can you talk about because
essentially
what we're talking about
is succession planning
for the stacks ideal hero.
If hero is working
in the business,
he can't work
on the business.
Is that fair? Hero?
I mean,
I never look at it
from that way, but,
I just want to,
Yeah.
Create more.
The more
capable leaders they are.
An ecosystem doesn't have
to be just an AI guild.
So the so rocket given
you know
what hero wants to do
so of thing off hero.
I just want to nail this
before I forget it.
Brock, you've talked about
your journey.
Can you,
give me some situation?
Task action results
for the other mentees,
including myself.
Situation.
So, I mean,
I think it starts
with, like,
identifying
where you're at right now.
So can you use, like,
Aiden as an example?
Right.
Sure.
So I mean,
with Aiden, he,
I mean, I met him when
he was like, what, 17?
Right?
He still in high school
trying to figure out
what he wants
to do with college
and him himself
being a techie,
like he was trying to
decide, like,
do I go to college
or do I, like,
hack it out right, and
just do a startup or join
a startup, start working,
do a bootcamp, right?
Because college
is very expensive, right?
And he shared with me
that, his dad,
I think his dad works
as a Coast Guard.
And so he gets benefits
like government benefits
through the GI
Bill. Right.
And so as he finishes
community college
pays for that. And there's
like subsidies for that.
If you
go to community college,
he gets paid
to go to a university,
which he's doing right
now, like in this
like the next week or two.
Right.
And so I told him that's
like a no brainer, right?
Because,
instead of competing
with all of these other,
like, you know, boot camp
graduates, right,
you'll
actually have a degree.
And later on,
if he wants to pursue,
you know,
a master's degree or a PhD
because he's he's
very smart, right.
He could do that. Right.
And so I think he thought
about it,
talked with his parents,
and he decided that
I think for him,
I mean, college
makes sense,
especially for two years
out of the four, he's
going to get paid
to go to
and learn stuff right.
So I think him assessing
his current
situation,
the s right in stark,
that painted
a better picture, right?
A more clearer picture
for him
to make that decision
because I can help him
through the process.
But I can't make that
decision for him.
Can you do the same thing
for, Christina
and then myself?
Sure.
So the situation for
Christina was that she,
already
had her bachelor's.
When I met her.
I met her through,
like, a family friend.
She was looking for a job
for six months already.
Right? And no luck. Right.
And so, the family
friend, you know,
I recently helped to land
a job,
and so,
like, word got around,
and then I helped my other
friend Kevin land a job
because he already was in
well into his career,
but he did sort of like
a pivot
where the job that he,
like, he,
he was more into, like,
hardware,
like electric engineering.
And he wanted to switch
to software
even though he had like a
bachelor's degree in CSS.
Right.
But when you,
most of your,
like, your,
resume is like hardware.
It's a little hard
to switch to software
when I'm doing that
pivot right.
And so helping him, like,
you know, going through
the star method,
like practicing
your interviews, right.
Really nailing down,
answering the question of,
tell me about yourself.
Right.
Like, I think that just
little difference
when you start out
really strong
in the interview
that helped him
land is your first
and so is your your first
and your most your first
and your last answer.
Because of the primacy
and recency effect,
it's probably something
that's very ignored
in interview coaching.
Yeah, I,
I think once they nail
that, it's
it makes it easy
like the rest
of the interview
so much easier.
Just figuring out
your beginning
and how to end strong.
Right. Get to next steps.
So and myself.
And for yourself,
I mean, yeah, I met
we met, here on spaces
because you were.
I was trying to find a job
through you
at that time.
It three years ago.
Yeah. Right.
And so, I mean, it was a
give and take, right?
Like I was learning
from you, right?
Yeah.
It's time
you were learning for me
on the coding side. Right.
And at the time, like, GPT
didn't
even really release yet
when we first met,
I think like shortly
after GPT released,
right, like three
GPT three.
Gosh, we're we're to you
two versions in the past.
Right. And so,
I mean, at that time,
we were just talking about
doing a hackathon, right?
And so that's where
how GPT
and the build
a thon sort of method
and event structure
kind of started.
Right?
Well, that all started
because
I stuck around this
because I knew I was bad
at sales.
Right.
And I wanted to learn from
you how to do sales.
And so, the book. Right.
I think it was after,
after my grandpa
passed, right, that,
that that December.
Right.
He passed
and then January,
I was like, okay,
I want to commit.
I was telling myself
I was going to I'll,
I always tell myself, I'm
going to read these books
and I never do.
Right.
So I think making
that commitment is like,
hey, I'm actually going to
read these books, right?
I'm actually
I'm going to use
AI to prompt it
and actually put it
into practice.
Right.
I think that made a huge
difference, right?
Using the PRD method,
using like spin
selling is, is a custom
GPT already, right?
It's not.
You know, I didn't even
have to make that.
It's already available.
And so using that
for all of our,
all of our calls,
all of our meetings,
and then
that really helped
get me to where I am today
as engineering manager.
So I'm going to ask you to
finish off the story
about myself,
because you understand
how I've gone
from front end,
the back end to full
apps now,
and now I'm using Haskell.
But then,
I'd also ask you, after
the finishing of the story
about myself and my,
development roadmap,
how you're thinking about
going
from mentoring individuals
to if you were in charge
of stacks
because of
what you know about DNS
and zero authority,
how we might bring this
all together?
Yeah.
So there's like
two parts to that.
So first part is
I think your journey.
Right.
I mean, I can't take
all the credit.
I mean, Paul,
it's someone
who taught you Python.
I'm like him
for all this chaos. Yes,
but he's going to
get a tractor
soon, so. Yes,
we got him. What?
Exactly
what he wanted, and more.
So, yeah,
we can't wait to see him
with his tractor.
It'll be fine.
Hey, and the other person,
who shall remain
nameless, has a house now.
And your house.
Wow. Okay. Yeah.
You did close on a task,
right? Right? Right.
Yeah, yeah.
That's true.
That is very true.
Yeah.
So keep going.
Don't take up.
You can't take
all the credit,
because Paul for me,
Python and but continue
because, you know, you.
Oh, if Oma is
great at back end,
you're great at front end.
And you help me actually
do these integration
of those two.
Yeah.
I mean, I think the, the
creation of like GPT 3.5.
Right.
Doing the build of thought
because we could have
like when we spend a ton
of hours on spaces, right.
Less now than, than
when we first started.
I think that all started
because we were
part of the,
you know, evil plan.
And his his, yes,
you know,
ongoing spaces last cycle.
Right.
Meeting all those people
there was very helpful.
Like all pretty much
most of the DeFi
knowledge that I know
today was from agencies
with Evil plan.
And I met you through
Eric who introduced.
Yeah.
And and we still talk
to some of those people
today.
Right. Like there.
So you know they might not
be in spaces as often
but they still jump on
every now and we catch up
with them. Right.
And so I think
for your journey,
doing the build of fans
really, really helped
because it like actually
focused our energy
instead of just talking
about ideas all day.
We actually put
like, people
put money on the line.
Right?
It started with $10
and then it was 100
and then into the
thousands. Right.
And then, you know,
the whole project
with, Doctor Wetzel.
Right.
Like we basically got
someone paid
the level who works
for the US government
to show up to our like,
that's
that was pretty cool.
Okay. So it's really cool.
And he wasn't
the first celebrity
to show up
at these spaces.
Yeah.
And I learned a lot
from those faces.
Right. Oh, yeah.
And sure, like,
I think like they got a,
like, we didn't
get to the finish line
for some of the projects.
Okay.
But we learned a lot in
like throughout
the journey. Right.
And that's pretty typical
with like startup culture.
Right.
Is not to get
sort of disappointed and
sort of dejected
from the failures.
Right.
Just focus on
what we actually learned.
And we learned a lot
like it was the first time
that I learned about,
like, was it, common
graph complexity?
Was it? Right?
Right.
Well, actually.
So, I
want to really nail this
because I believe that
the future of any guild
is build a thons, right?
You know how we're doing
our sprints
and one hour,
our Google venture
design sprints with you
and sometimes
and how we'll be there
in the background.
That's the future,
I think, of
intentional collaboration
with definable outcomes.
Give it that work expands
to fill the time allotted.
Can you talk about.
It's something
we haven't talked about.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Was bring this on you
back.
You didn't have a job
before the build a phone,
but you got one after.
Yeah. Right.
But what changed?
Well GPT 3.5 coming out.
Definitely say more.
Say more about that.
Sure. So,
so another another
sort of like, career
coach that I follow,
online.
He was talking about,
like,
the way that you get
promoted quickly
and like, by
your manager is to make
his life easier.
Right?
And it's not to just
follow everything
that he does. Right.
Because they're busy.
Right.
And for myself, like,
I mean,
I have a girlfriend
and I have to spend time
with her,
but I don't have, like,
kids, right.
I don't have
kids of my own.
I don't have to, like,
spend time with kids.
I don't have, like.
Like, my parents
aren't, like, all.
And I have to take care
of them, right?
But for him, like,
he probably has parents
like my manager. Right?
He has parents. The
he has to take care of.
He has young kids.
He has to take care of.
He doesn't have time
to freaking read
like all these AI updates.
Right.
And and stay up to date
with,
you know,
whatever GPT model is out
and whatever
tool is available, right.
And so
I really started with
doing the build with on
and learning pretty much
everything that we could
in the two weeks that
we did the build phone.
Right.
Not even two weeks or far,
like a weekend
plus like five days.
Right.
So like a week
that we learned to really
nail down what, what
the ins and outs
and the weaknesses
right, of GPT 3.5.
And then
during the interview,
I just talked
about my projects
and what we did for
the build, the timeline
and everything I knew
about ChatGPT for pretty
much like 40 minutes
out of the hour
during the interview,
right? Sure.
We went the the normal.
Tell me about yourself,
talk about my career,
what my plans are
for the future,
why I'm interested
in the company.
Right. Typical behavior.
Questions
for an interview.
And then he asked about
my personal projects,
and I was like, sure,
I'm doing,
you know, I started
this build a farm,
this group on X, right?
He was very interested,
and I just talked about
that for the rest
of the interview. Right.
And even
throughout the job,
all these updates for AI
and how we can use it
at the company,
like I'm basically,
you know, unofficially
chief AI officer
at the company because
no one knows what to do.
The updates
are super fast.
It's like every week.
They're, you know, each
knowing what to do
is not a trivial thing.
And if you're not
confused,
you're not paying
attention.
Can you say more about
just how difficult it is,
even for very
intelligent people
because of the pace of
change to actually use it?
Yeah.
I mean, like
most of my coworkers,
like, have kids, right?
Like, I'm probably
the youngest person
at the company.
Right.
And,
you know, I,
I'm trying to put myself
in their shoes, like,
you know, when you're busy
just doing life things
right, you don't have time
to consistently and,
you know, almost to
to the point of abuse,
like prompt to cloud code
right down to your life.
Like,
that's not a normal thing
that people do.
Yeah.
Normal people
aren't up at 5:38 a.m.
trying to
create a real package.json
for the railway
hackathon at 12 p.m..
Yeah, and
so like, it's not
about like
sharing everything
that I do
because a lot of
the things I do like,
they fail. Right.
But the things
that are successful,
I do use them as
suggestions
to my, my manager.
Right.
And then some of that
gets, you know,
it moves up
the chain of command.
Right?
And it makes its way
to our CEO. Right.
Because he has the time.
And that's like his entire
job, right?
You know,
so using the signal
processing
filtering system
for the executive team
and peers and then
and the subordinates.
Yeah.
So, it kind of goes
both ways.
So like I'm doing more of
like the day to day
ground work discovery
right into
whether it's AI or machine
learning systems.
Right, or Shopify.
Right.
Because that makes
all of our money right.
While so that's like
bottom up, right.
And then top down, our CEO
and I think most CEOs,
right, are looking at
the release of GPT five.
What is Google's response?
What is meta doing?
Do I use AI right.
And how do you I use this
to make more money
for my investors
because most companies
have stakeholders, right?
And I don't
how do I
architect these systems
such that migrating
to a new paradigm
is not a transformation
that takes billions
of dollars and 18 months?
I mean,
it's expensive to adopt
any new technology, right?
As well
as, if you choose the
wrong one, it's
very costly.
Right.
We're making budgeting
decisions right now
in the WhatsApp. Okay.
What are we going to do?
So. Right.
So, can you now again
start to do this?
Can you talk about
just how fundamentally,
the code is changing
your workflow
and specifically
for the stack saying, Gil,
can you talk about
the process
of how you created
the video
that we just created above
using the filmmaker
context engineering
with Cloud code
to develop the Json
for the video
for Midjourney?
Well,
I think it just started
with like, me
wanting to make,
so so we're doing like
a pitch for at least I.
Right.
It's going to be like
a health
and wellness
companion, right?
Tool, and it's going to be
customer facing,
that we're we're looking
at release in in January.
Right. And
I wanted to
make better, website
assets.
Right.
So in, in front end
development or,
web design,
you know,
you know, those,
those boxes, those square
rectangular boxes
and have
it has like
a little bit of text,
but there's usually like
some kind of illustration
or, some kind of video
that's like background
video that's playing
or some animation
that's playing.
So that if you want
a prompt
for this, it's called,
like a bento box, right.
Or a bento section. Right.
And so those sections,
if you're really good
at designing,
you're going to animate
these things, right?
Usually in After Effects.
And it's very time
consuming and expensive
to do it.
Right.
And so I was having
trouble prompting it.
And, you know, that
specific example
is not for the bento box.
Right.
But I
was having some trouble
crafting the
prompts for Midjourney,
right where it would look
good and, you know,
good enough, right,
for an MVP, right?
Because
this is potentially,
that landing page
would potentially allocate
anywhere between 200
and 50 K to half
$1 million
of internal investments,
right from the CEO
and the CFO.
Right.
Because I'm essentially
asking for funds
internally
to do this project.
Right.
And so if we're going to
ask for a quarter million
to half $1 million,
it's going to have to look
pretty damn good, right?
It's gonna look
it has to look convincing.
And so we just Midjourney
has a lot of nuances,
right?
That may or may not be
different from other
prompting tools. Right.
And I was struggling
with that.
And so, I mean, the idea
came from you, Michael.
Right, is let's figure out
let's write a tool
to help me
write the Json right,
to dump into Midjourney.
So let's not like
prompt it,
manually because I'm
not a film director
and you know that.
Remind us.
Yeah.
And, you know,
I was asking
you and you're like,
I don't know, you know,
right.
Let's
fucking have planets.
Yeah.
And and so, you know, we
we kind of like,
you know co prompted
madness and GPT
and came up with the Json
structure to give us a way
to better direct video.
Right.
And so that came about
because we were trying
to come up with ideas
for the current,
CTC.
Like hackathon
that's going on.
So we're a part of that.
We're doing that
on Dora Hacks.
I think the the end date
is September 4th.
But yeah, we'll see
if we can use these tools
to make a cool
landing page,
you know,
do some marketing
and then actually create
the, the payment gateway
with Sbdc
with, cloud code.
So in we're
going to come to that,
but I want to have
some overlap.
What was the
what was the difference
between the generated
videos and images
you got with Midjourney
when you started?
And after the sprint,
where we developed
a data structure
to act as a film director,
what was the change like
in using in
creating content in videos
and images
with Midjourney?
Sure.
So I think I just
I didn't know
how to describe things.
Right.
Because I'm not like
a, I'm not I didn't take
I mean,
I took like
a photography class
in like high school,
right.
But I'm not into like
film.
Just watch
a lot of content. Right.
So I know when the content
looks good, right.
Because it just consume
a lot of content. Right.
But I don't really know
how to describe it
into words.
And with these, prompt,
like engines, basically,
they only understand
words, right?
But but with Midjourney,
it's not just even words.
It's all of these
parameters
that you have to know.
Right?
Like I totally forgot
about Nietzsche.
So I was like,
oh, if you do not need it.
And it's like optimize for
like anime style, right?
Prompts.
Like, how do I do like
camera movements, right?
I didn't really know
how to describe that.
And I totally forgot
that you could even,
in my brain,
I was putting images
that I generated
as references
like style references,
but you could also
just references it
like through the words
right?
And so just using things
like,
you know,
the favorite anime
that I want
it to look like, right.
And so,
being able to describe
things like that without,
being super specific.
Right?
I think at some point
I'll get used to it
and I'll remember
certain things,
but I think is a great
tool for beginners, right?
I mean,
I think we should just
make to the web apps
honestly inherent.
So what was the,
what was the difference
between the, outputs
that you got before
implementing this cloud
code film director engine?
And what was the
difference after
when you actually did
the outputs?
It's at the top for anyone
who wants to see it.
I mean, the difference
was huge, right?
Yeah. Like the other one.
I can only just do
like simple movements.
And it wasn't consistent.
Right.
Like there was one
where I was trying
to get it to do,
like a drone fly over,
but I didn't really know
how to describe, like,
I want you to fly,
you know, the drone from
bottom left to like, top
right, right.
And then, you know, still
centering on the object.
Right.
And it was just like,
inconsistent
and didn't
look as good. Right.
So now,
I mean, now it's just
more consistent
because like the,
the AI prompt optimizer is
the one taking my words,
my descriptions
and then structuring it in
a way where
Midjourney will understand
it best
and not my understanding
of Midjourney.
So given that the stacks
AI guild right now
has the outcome
of cementing
as positioning
in the customer's mind
stacks as the dominant
layer two in Bitcoin,
how can you share
with others
how you've used cloud code
with context engineering
to create better outputs
with Midjourney?
Good will video,
what have you.
I mean, I think I just
have to just post more.
I mean, I think
the both of you posted.
Yeah, right.
I think, I mean,
I think I need to like
maybe part of linear
is like actually
having a social project,
like a social media
where I dedicate time
to actually posts
consistently.
Right?
Because people
only see your effects
through me and Aiden
and Cristine. Right.
Does that make sense?
Yeah.
Like they see
a lot of your work
through other people
in the syndicate.
Yeah.
I mean, I think now that,
you know,
finally got that
official title. Yes.
I don't have to worry
as much now.
It's just
I just got to cruise
for at least six months.
Right?
If I wanted to hop,
I probably could.
I really like it
here. Right?
I don't really plan to hop
anytime soon.
Right.
But, Nah,
I think now is pretty
much the time to, the
how do you say it?
To, to
what is it
to come out of stealth?
Yeah.
Emerge from stealth.
Emerge from stealth? Yes.
I think,
if there was ever a time
for you as an individual
to emerge from stealth,
now wouldn't
be the worst time.
You're not just
a front end developer.
No offense.
You know what I mean?
And I say that
from the perception
of statuses on the,
you know, kind of thing.
You have
a bit of status now.
It'll take a little time
to kick in.
I'm sure you'll come.
And then you can,
you know, eventually
become uncle Bob.
You know,
that be the long arc.
Okay, great.
So going back, let's
put a fine point on it.
The purpose of this tax
ideal is to secure
the positioning of stocks
in the magic
Quadrant for Gartner,
for lay
or choose on Bitcoin.
Is that fair?
I want to know what hero
thinks.
Is that fair? Hero?
Is that
what we're going for?
I mean, one of the things,
that I want to see
from the other artists,
too, and, sax AI Guild is
I would like to see
their process.
Right.
Maybe one of them has
a really cool tool that we
don't know about that
often prompts.
Well,
one of the great things is
three
Hana has been posting
videos
through the organize media
which this process.
So you can
imagine what we can do
with that data set.
In addition
to this conversation,
one of
the key things that is,
going to
take us tax
ideals to the next level
is to turn a collection
of individuals into a
network of individuals.
Does that make sense?
Just like you and I
and the rest of the team
are networks to GitHub.
I can combine
this conversation today
with 300 transcripts
from the organize media
to start
building a curriculum.
No hierarchy in back.
You can keep going.
I've already hit my hour
limit for today.
Yeah, yeah. Thank.
It's like you're on
air too long.
It's okay. So,
now to return to
where we were initially.
The reason
I open this space.
It's actually not stacks
related.
But it is member
audio box.
Not fun.
I do remember that
experiment we did to
use code to create music.
Yeah,
with, frisky fisticuffs.
Right? Yeah.
So remember how I told you
I learned, how
to kind of think
and programing Haskell
with a matrix?
So I was like, oh,
so you're saying that
Haskell is a better tool
for state management,
than other paradigms?
And, grok said, yeah.
So I was like, all right,
now that is a matrix.
You know how I have
Geometry of Music
and create remixes
by arranging songs?
Okay. Yeah.
I remember
you wanted to make a tool
and give people access
to that
as part of your teaching,
right?
Of geometry, of music.
I have it working
now for a single song.
Nice.
Katy Perry's
Harleys in Hawaii.
You'll understand this.
You're familiar
with a chord progression.
You're
familiar that most songs
consist of a repeat of the
same chord progression
over and over again?
Yeah, pretty much
just shift
it between verse, chorus,
bridge, B chorus, bridge.
All right. Intro.
Yeah.
I mean, most of the songs
don't
even have bridges
or tags anymore.
No, no,
it's like chorus, chorus,
maybe a verse and then.
Yeah.
Is the TikTok
ification of music, right?
So, but what if we took
every 16 or 32 bars
of the vocals
as bricks, vocal bricks,
and we rearranged
and layered and
create multi layers
of vocal bricks
that went over
the same instrumental.
That's
what I have right now.
So I have it for Katy
Perry's Hawaii
generated about 5
to 8 different remixes.
Now what
I'm going to do is
I'm going
to use myself, the human,
to take the best parts
of those remixes
and create a final one,
because a lot
of the opinions on AGI,
AI is an AI that works
without human input.
But I believe that
no AI is complete
without the signal
processing
of humans interacting
with each other
to document the song piece
that cannot be
necessarily structured
or communicated
in text.
My eyes crawling
data alone.
Does that make sense?
So I'm purposefully
inserting myself
in the process.
Yeah, I think
when we talk about AGI
we have to define
like our definition of it.
I think
the VC definition of AGI
is that you know, open AI,
they're going to link AGI,
right?
Google.
They're going to make AGI.
And they have to say that
they're going to
they're not going to say
so AGI is actually
a complex network of
networks
right next to that.
Their stock is going to
drop because the thesis is
not that.
Their thesis is I'm going
to help you fire people.
My thesis
is I'm going to help you
allocate
your human capital
more strategically now
that we have a new tool
to take the burden of,
if them thinking off
their hands.
We're seeing this play out
with,
with, like L2 too,
right?
Like, like circle
is creating their own
aetherium L2 like tether
is doing their own L2.
Pretty much
all the major things
I want to do there.
So you're saying
we're going to have
the basic application
of L2
where the exchanges
create their own L2?
I mean, it's
it was like it's
very similar instance
in the 2000s
when everyone wanted
to create their own
internet.
Right?
The narrative back
then was like,
oh, internets will be
the best thing ever,
and it will be
the internet as a whole,
because private is better,
safer, right?
Faster, cheaper. Right?
That did become the case.
Like the whole internet
as a whole
is much, much bigger
and much more valuable
than any single internet
that a single company
can create.
I mean,
I guess,
I guess you could say
that in certain
countries, Facebook
is their internet, right?
I don't think that's
the only
way that they get access.
Yeah.
So that's the net net
of my, explorations
right now with Haskell,
I was able to go from,
you know, creating
applications with back
ends of Python,
flask, Django
to an end to rust, Tmax.
And now I'm starting
to think
in Haskell,
like I'm
talking about pre pre.
I think in Haskell
create the groups
and the monoids
and the functors and the
objects and the entities.
And then let's create
the pod
that's faithful to that.
Using the Haskell program
as a way to
logically evaluate
what we're asking,
what we're proposing.
Yeah I think yeah,
I think you're on the
wrong blockchain.
You sound more
and more like a card.
Yeah. Sorry. Okay.
So actually
that's another thing.
So Cardano
has a hackathon.
So we're going to be
submitting to that, right?
I think this,
because the other
thing, I'm looking at you
is the reason I'm
starting with Haskell is
I, I didn't execute
the solution in the end.
And Haskell,
I had the Haskell
developer
talk to the Python
in the presence
of the product manager,
and I ended up having
the Python developer
complete the task.
Does that make sense?
So a thought in Haskell.
But then it executed in
Python
and I have
the whole conversation.
So now I'm
speaking in rules.
Make sense?
I used to
just speak 1 to 1 as
if ChatGPT was one person.
Now I'm saying we're going
to have a conference
simulate a conversation.
See, this is why
I want to be able to like,
have like shared
kind of like program
like code
programing or paragraphs,
but in a prompt sense,
right?
Like like I wanted it.
So I so far
it's one of the reasons
why I love granola.
Right.
The the meeting recorder
and transcriber.
It's because I could live
prompt granola.
Right.
Have it
come up with questions,
have it come,
you know, make me sound
smart or whatever.
Sometimes,
most of the time
it's probably, like,
not useful, right?
Like,
I probably have better
contacts, right,
than granola itself,
but it
it direct me in the right
path, and that's
really all I really need
the tool to do.
Just point
me in the right direction.
And the other engineers
love it, by the way,
because I post the recaps
into our slack channels.
I love it.
Yeah,
people who can't show up,
they appreciate it
or they have to have
early.
They like the recap,
and the people who stay,
you know, are able
to prompt it as well
when I post it.
If they, like,
don't understand
something that I said.
That is a key part
where I realize that
if we're going to become
better as a team, it's
the network effects
between us,
which is
now driven to GitHub
because I can post repos
and now you have my repos
with the full readings,
but I'm writing a read me
intended for an Ela lab
because I know you're
not going to fucking
look at the code.
You're going to have cloud
code,
look at the code and
and from cloud code
to tell you
about the GitHub
and the project structure
and the key files.
So I'm also thinking about
the developer experience
which is mediated by an.
Hey maybe
we can make this tool.
How do how do we do
pair pair
prompting with cloud code.
So so what I'm going to do
for example,
is I'm going to, export
this full chat.
I have a few ways of kind
of investigating this,
you know, just kind of
exploring the space.
But right now
I have a conference
between a product manager,
the Haskell person,
and the Python person.
So I'm getting used to
coordinating
between agents.
That makes sense.
There's the task master.
So, you know,
what's going to happen
is I'm going to
get that code today
or tomorrow, right.
And there's going to be
an explosion.
So to end this
conversation off,
which is good,
can you talk about
how we're going
to interact in the future
using linear
and how different that is
from how we're interacting
right now?
What's happened
that is the key
inflection point for us.
Sure.
I mean,
eventually I don't think
we're going to stop
using WhatsApp.
I think we need to use
cloud code to make
some kind of plug
in for WhatsApp.
So like we can do
something
like, slash Claude,
you know, take this
to summarize our last hour
into a list of action
items.
We just directly in
WhatsApp. Right.
And then push to linear
as tickets.
And we can do things
like that now,
which is pretty
was pretty cool.
Other other things
that I'm doing
with cloud code
is, for work.
I'll have a session
with it where it's like
it'll come up
with like a plan MD right?
And then it's like, okay,
take this actually came
from my manager,
by the way.
So I'm
sharing ideas with him,
and then he's coming up
with his own workflows
and sharing it
with everybody else.
Let me let me
you're going to
share what he did.
So step one is you use
cloud to write a PRD,
right.
Have it asks you at least
ten questions.
You answer it,
you provide requirements,
maybe code
snippets, entire code base
constraints,
write security measures,
and then you ask it
to decompose the PRD
into sprints.
And so our sprints are
two weeks, two weeks long.
Monday
through Friday. Right.
If you want,
I give it context
where Friday
is typically lighter
because
some of our contractors
don't work on Fridays.
Right.
So it's going to issue
last tickets
around Thursday
and Friday. Right.
And then step three
is to take the sprints
and make a to do DMD.
Breaking the sprints down
into individual task.
If tasks are complex
and have a high
number
for story points, right.
Create
subtask within those task.
Right.
And then you can even
it's depending on the
task, you can even issue
that to do
task two clawed sub agents
to do the writing
and stuff for you
and then dump it
into another markdown file
or some kind of code.
Right.
And then you just repeat
and do that
whenever you have
a new set of work to do.
So I mean, that's, that's
what my VP of engineer.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Precisely. So,
to me,
the ability to implement
these rules,
right, as system
prompts, as agents
allow us to move from
having
to focus on coordination
to just making sure that
we get the right signal
during the transcripts
of our human
to human conversations.
Does that make sense?
I mean, I would
do it to this call, right?
So that's exactly
what we're going to do
re transcribe it.
There's probably
so I, I usually have
three sections.
So the first section is
what was decided
is typically
the meetings thing.
So we have,
we have to decide what
the course of action is.
Right.
And then the other section
is next steps.
So these are more like
more every right.
There's no specific person
that has to do anything.
But it's more like
look into something
something right.
Or you know,
our next step is
to do some discovery
into as BTC,
payment
gateway with Shopify.
Right. But then that
the last section
is the action items.
And so action
items are more specific.
And so you actually
assign it with a person
with the name or the team.
Right. With a name.
And so, you know,
you divide things
into that
and then you assign it
to someone on linear
to get a notification.
And then
you just do the work.
Or the
AI is doing the work,
you assign it to cloud.
I phone
that, can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you.
I think that's a sign
that it's time to get off.
Yeah.
So let's,
If you were to suggest,
some of the elements
that the HCI would pay
attention to, again,
you don't
necessarily.
Does that make sense?
But what are the key
things
that you would suggest
that the AI focus on,
even if it's just,
you know,
not related to stacks
AI Guild,
but helps everything
overall?
Like for myself,
I think it just comes down
to how do we build up
distribution channels?
For me personally,
I mean, maybe that means
building up
like more content,
posting more often,
more regularly.
I think we made a great
bet on Nate n
that it will
become popular
and it will become useful,
and I think we need to
double down on that. That
like, I
think that's a pretty safe
bet to learn and
and from the ground up.
Right.
Learn all the changes,
whatever the struggle is.
Right.
Because I know that, like,
maybe the docs aren't,
updated or like,
you know,
and had an update recently
and, you know, maybe
cursor is very good at it
yet with a new context,
but we just need to
overcome that hurdle,
maybe create our own
version of the docs.
Right.
Provide that as markdown
contacts, whatever it is.
Right.
I think for our team,
getting really,
really good at no end
is going to
give us a lot of leverage,
especially since I have
this freaking PC
that has 64 gigs,
about gigabytes of Ram,
and a ton of memory.
That's like
not doing anything right.
Originally
we were going to run local
lmms on it,
but then Open Router has a
ton of different models
that we can
just use for free,
that are way faster.
Right.
And so now
how do we reallocate this
resource that is my
PC as well as Aiden's PC,
because he has both a
mac and a PC
that has plenty of memory
and GPU power
to just run things.
I have a suggestion
for a decision
and next steps.
How might we take in the.
Mid journey
prompt?
Process,
which acts as a
PhD and film direction
into an end point
such that the stacks
I Guild creators
can take their prompts
or their ideas
and just like you did,
get ten x to 100 x
Jason prompts,
which are under 1000
characters, so whatever.
So for me is
so I've already assigned
sort of, this is like
the third priority
of a project for Aiden.
So he already knows and
and right.
I think the next thing
that he needs help with is
we need Vance back.
I know he, you know, he's
he's doing his thing.
He's got family
obligations. Right?
But he's our stable
diffusion local.
That's relative image
and video I perked up.
Yeah.
And maybe we don't
wait for him.
Maybe we connect with Jim.
Right?
Maybe we connect with
maybe someone here
in this room
and I go over this one.
What if I use this
conversation
to create an agent
that has a conversation
with him?
So when he's driving,
he can just provide us
and therefore
everyone the.
And does
that make sense. Yeah.
Yeah.
So maybe we take
the the granola notes.
Yeah.
Create a notebook
like notebook out
loud recap for him
that he can just listen to
as like a podcast.
Yes. So he knows what
his next steps
and his action items are.
Well so what
I'm thinking is,
is I'm
starting to really derive
a lot of benefit
from 11 lapses.
One of the next steps
is I'm going to convert
this conversation
into one of the outputs
is going to be a system
prompt for an 11 lapse
agent that can have
a conversation
with Vance.
Does that make sense?
Yeah. Right.
So we can entertain
and comfy
everything
that we're doing.
Right now
because I think that
if we can do anything
that's helpful,
it's to help people
create better prompts.
And if they want to learn
how, they can learn how.
But the initial step
is ten x.
My prompt.
I'm sure I'm not
the only person who wants
or is trying to design
something at the prompt.
And from what
I've seen, I'm biased.
It's you and three Hannah
that has the best
pieces of content
right now.
With ball,
you pick and Nozpheratu
and GG for this stuff.
And so,
that's what I'm thinking.
So for Stack's I Guild,
which wants to position
itself
as the dominant layer two
for Bitcoin
and mindshare Gartner
Magic Quadrant.
The purpose of the stacks
I guild in relation to
that goal is to create,
media and social campaigns
and marketing campaigns
that achieve
the impressions
and the views
and the comments
and the likes and the tags
that are so important
to crossing the chasm
and having a plus one
Net Promoter score
and so,
one of the decisions is to
help ten x
all of the creators
make their problems
better.
But the
other piece is to,
Encourage
collaboration more.
Have I missed anything?
Rocky?
No, I think that's good.
I think
one of the things that
I thought of is, like,
there are other people
that I follow on X,
right,
that are great creators
and they're they're
I have already figure it
out sort of the source
within the prompts.
Right, right.
I think what I need to do
is like as I'm generating
them,
like actually post them
as a reply
to those very same people.
That's where
all my bookmarks. Right.
Like,
let's not do it in silo.
But like he's like, hey,
I use your prompt.
And this is
what came out like,
how do I improve this?
Right?
Maybe they respond w
fantastic, right?
Well, maybe
they don't respond. Right.
But I think doing more of
that is going to be good
just for you.
Just for my own
improvements.
Right.
But I think that's part of
how do you build up
distribution
channels as well.
And my
final question, we are
participating in the Dora
Hacks as BTC hackathon.
And you've alluded
to the SDC and Shopify.
Can you talk about your
background with Shopify
and why you chose this
as an outcome?
And then, talk about how
we're going to use linear
to manage
this next process
and this next
phase of the build a thons
where we do a build on
every single day,
sometimes three of them
at the same time.
Yeah.
Well, I, I found
I found it through Dora
Hacks right from the other
I think the other one was
the AI one that we did.
Right.
A couple of months back,
I believe.
So why Shopify?
Well, because base
has an integration
with Shopify, right?
I think right now
a lot of the things
that we're building on
stacks
is like built in silo.
Right.
And that's not
what vendors want.
Right?
Like you're
you're going to share this
to my CEO.
He's going to be like,
what is connect
with right.
We're making all
of our money on Shopify.
Right.
Why does it matter
that I'm capturing,
you know, $10,000 on this
obscure blockchain?
Like they're not even care
about that shit.
They're
making $30 million.
So we have
to integrate with systems
that already have high
liquidity.
Right.
And so, you know, my
ten years in e-commerce
and building
mostly on Shopify, right?
I've done WordPress,
right.
But Shopify makes it
super simple and easy.
And there's a reason
why Shopify partnered up
with, with with base
chain with Coinbase
and partnered up
with stripe
to get this done right.
And guess what?
A lot of that
information is public.
They literally wrote
a blog post
on how to build a payment
gateway on Shopify
for blockchains.
Right?
So instead of
just building
like a random gateway
that only works for this
one super custom obscure
vendor to,
build it for the largest,
you know, direct
to consumer e-commerce
platform
that you can think of.
And to me, that Shopify.
And, what's our niche that
we're going to focus on
and what demonstrate
what's the demonstration
going to show?
Sure.
So assuming that we can
take payments, right.
There's no reason why
we can't take donations.
Right.
And so as,
part of the add on
or plug in to the payment
gateway is
we want to let nonprofits
be able to accept as BTC
and St as part
of donations
and businesses.
So I'm not talking
like ten, right, $100.
Right?
Sure.
Like people who donate
that much,
they might want a receipt.
But if you're a business
and you're donating
thousands,
if not tens of thousands,
hundreds
of thousands of dollars
to any nonprofit
that you know
has a mission
that they believe in,
they will want a receipt,
right, for the IRS,
especially if you're here
in the United States.
Right.
Because,
they're going to
want to claim
that as a tax write off.
Right.
And so,
you know,
maybe it's to offset
other gains, maybe
it's to do some, you know,
interesting,
creative accounting.
Right. Creative finance.
They're going
to want a receipt
and they're not going
to want to pay,
you know, a couple
hundred dollars extra
because
they're a nonprofit.
They don't have
a ton of money.
They rather spend a couple
hundred dollars
on their project or
furthering their mission.
Right.
So instead of, having
the, the businesses,
pay for specialized
accounting software,
let's build a tool
that looks up on the block
explorer, right,
and generate
an actual receipt
for the people
who are donating. Right.
Then they can put that
into it, into their IRS
form and file it up,
or save it somewhere.
Right.
And I think that's going
to encourage more,
donations
to nonprofit projects.
So imagine
you're narrating the demo,
and in their mind's eye,
your narration is going
to paint the picture.
How's the demo work that
we're submitting to a tax?
Well,
I think we do, the spin
method.
Right. What is the current
situation?
Right.
The current situation is
that CTC
is difficult to use.
Right?
We don't have a,
you know, what are the,
the major e-commerce
platforms
that we're connected in?
How do nonprofits today
take donations on stacks?
Right.
Well, we're
building the solution
with this MVP, right?
The problem is that
the UI, UX is not good.
The other problems
is that,
as users, you may want
a receipt, right?
When you're donating
to a nonprofit
through a payment gateway
and be able to generate
a receipt either.
So you can file it in
your tax
return at the end
of the year. Right.
And so, what are the
what are the implications
of not solving this?
Well, the implication is,
TVL on stacks
does not grow.
Transaction volume
continues to plateau.
If not, go down. Right.
And the net payoff
is if we do
solve this problem, right,
then merchants
and vendors
are able to deploy,
stacks payment gateway
with CTC, with Shopify,
one of the
largest e-commerce
platforms on the planet.
It you last time
we talked about,
you know, on chain
Nigerians.
Well, well, Shopify
it works in Nigeria.
It also works
in South Africa.
So if anyone there
wants to start
a Shopify store,
you can and accept as BTC.
And by the time
this is in production,
sorry, did you take
this to my final prompt?
Now that we've done
the spin is pitch
anything?
Pitch anything starts
with high contract,
high impact visual people
doing things over time.
And then
we talk about the
three markets that you've
already talked about,
which is, come
creating this opportunity,
which is the need for
donations and liquidity
for charities
and the need for
BTC to flow
and the need for there
to be a receipt
for regulatory
and political
and legal reasons.
And then we have the big
idea with interest priced
high morality.
So without having to do
all of those things
in that order, that's just
a pitch anything model.
Now that you've
articulated
the problem worth
solving or job to be done
or outcome
for, charities who want
to accept donations in
digital synthetic bitcoin
that is kosher
for political, legal
and regulatory bodies
to which they must comply.
How would you pitch this
now that you've discussed
the spin?
I think the picture comes.
You gotta come in strong
with expertise, right?
Like,
I think for myself, it's
the ten years
in e-commerce, right?
Earlier
you talked about, Now
I'm in, sort of,
a place of authority,
I suppose, a little bit
with the engineering
manager expertise.
Right.
I mean, just,
I think we do a deep
research on
how much money gets
transacted on Shopify.
Right.
Look at other examples.
You know,
we do compute competitor
research, right?
Our direct competitor
is going to be based
chain, right.
They got this huge backing
from Coinbase.
And they're already
integrated with base pay
right to pay with Usdc
with Shopify.
Right.
And so if we want to
keep up,
we're going to have
to create a Shopify
payment
gateway, to, to compete
with all these other alts.
So there's an opportunity
for competition
or cooperation, so to
speak, where you kind of
cooperate
with your competitors
to, chop up the market
share, our total,
addressable market.
So last thing, Rocky.
So, for this final phase,
can you,
we've done the spin.
Can you just explain it
to the door hacks, folks?
Very, succinctly
one last time for this
Sbdc donation.
We understand
why we want to do it now.
Why you
why you specifically?
So it's a combination
of only about yourself
and then tell me
what you're going to do,
which is essentially
what you've already done
because of your experience
is not something
you think you can do.
This is something
you already know
how to do,
and you have cloud code
to do it for you. Now.
Yeah, I think answering
the question about why
I do it right, I mean,
I think the history of,
you know, volunteer work,
working with nonprofits,
I think that's a strong
why for me,
for everything
that we do.
Right,
whether it's Exponent
Labs, whether it's my day
job. Right.
I think end
goal is for myself
is to run charity
gifts. Right.
Being able to take, like
I, I think corporate
gifting is a $60 billion
market and growing.
Right.
And being able
to leverage my already
my knowledge of Shopify,
being able to connect it
to nonprofit,
nonprofit projects and,
you know, visions
and projects
that I believe in. Right.
And now combine
that with stacks, right?
Like if if nonprofit
profits are able to accept
SPC and St
and earn a yield
right on chain
and be able to further
stretch out their,
project funding goals,
that's that's a strong
MTP to me, right?
That is the massive
transformative purpose
is being able to help
nonprofits, being able
to stretch their already
thin funds
to further their project
longer and better
and to be more effective.
Right.
That would be my why?
And, sorry,
this is the final one.
I would I'll,
I'll give you the prompt
to start with.
Hello.
My name is Rocky
and I'm a blanket blank.
And what we're going to be
submitting to the Dora
hacks SPC hackathon
is the following.
Prototype and demo.
Well, okay.
Hello, my name is Rocky.
I am,
now, engineering manager
at Elite Team Health.
Ten years experience
working with Shopify
Plus and vendors, helping
vendors scale
from a million RR to,
beyond 30 million RR.
And so today we're
delivering an MVP
for an SP, BTC payment
gateway to nonprofit
organization,
accept donations
as well as generate,
receipts
based on on chain data,
so that nonprofits can,
utilize the blockchain
more efficiently
with better, easier
to use, user experiences.
I have
nothing left to say.
How do you feel about how,
Now, I'd like you to.
Sorry.
This is the final one, but
this is good for the AGI.
What did you notice?
What did you like?
What didn't you like?
What would you change and
how would you change it?
About the way
that I hosted today's
session.
You better recording this
you than it is recording.
Yeah.
Because, No,
I mean, I think the,
the prompting style is
good.
I mean,
I was hoping that
more people would come up
and we can ask them
questions, right?
I think heroes doing
something else right now.
Yeah.
I mean, the style is fine.
Maybe. Yeah.
I'm hoping eventually,
like, we actually have,
we have
Cindy back, likely.
And I would love to just
prompt the AI directly
and just co collaborate,
live in spaces again
with and align
very soon.
I am not going to be
the one host
in this space.
Does that make sense.
And so just to put a fine
point on it,
what did you notice
about how I hosted today?
Space. What you like,
what didn't you like?
What would you change and
how would you change it?
Again,
you don't have to worry
about hurting my feelings
because these signals
are being processed
by someone else
or something else. Now.
I mean, I would love
to get feedback
from the listeners
and people
in the room, right?
Because I think sometimes
we, say things
or talk about things,
especially
like topics or subjects,
especially acronyms,
that other people
may not be familiar with.
Right?
So it depends on
who are we talking to.
Right.
If you're
talking to just me
and we're just recording
this for my sake,
you know, right. With,
you know, who my actual
intended audience is?
Who is that?
Dora hacks
and the Treasury.
Okay,
so now that you know
who the target market
of today's conversation
with is,
the Treasury Committee
and the door hacks who are
and who are in charge
of all of this funding,
how would you again
what did you like?
What didn't you like?
Now that you know,
my overall objective, I'm
sorry I didn't tell you
my overall objective,
I should have.
I don't want
to be manipulative,
but this recording today
was to demonstrate
how the syndicate operates
as a community within
the community, and stacks
seemed to be Cardano
and seem to be based.
Yeah.
I mean,
I think if we're targeting
the the
the hackathon organizers,
I think it's fine, but
we don't we also don't
want to assume,
that they are tactical.
Right.
Just because they're
running a technical
hackathon
doesn't necessarily mean
that they are technical.
Right.
And so being able
to explain things
in more plain language
would probably be good.
And this is for myself
too, right?
Because I'm so used to,
Shopify related terms.
Yeah.
So, I will say this,
The people in the
Treasury Committee or Dora
Hacks will never listen
to this full conversation.
They will only ever,
maybe get the Lem
summary
of this conversation
or see the demo as
they see the prototypes.
Does that make sense?
But yeah,
for the people
in those positions who are
looking to do funding,
my intention is that
today was a demonstration
of not only how
we think about things,
about the specific markets
that we're looking at
and also
the process of decision
making we go through
as we participate
in these hackathons.
And then they can decide
through their
underwriting team
whether we're
just wasting our breath
or actually doing
something significant.
I like it,
I hope the MDP and demo
videos will just speak
for themselves
once it's all done.
They didn't speak.
They changed reality
such that they had spoken.
Terry Pratchett
any final words?
Rocky?
No, I think it's good.
I think now we just run
into the transcript,
do the.
Let me get a summary
into action items
and go to linear
and start crunching away
that cool life.
So today, like
before we talked right.
It was WhatsApp
conversation.
Hey, we got to kick
this thing off.
And so I was like,
okay, perfect.
Let's kick this off.
This is this transfer
app will provide
more than enough data
for cloud code
to do the rest,
am I right?
Have we really missed
anything?
Nope.
I'm already running.
I already did
run like two hours
worth of deep research
with cloud. So
we are we already have
the contacts ready to go.
So my job and this is good
for the recording is
I am going to end
this Twitter space.
I'm going to use
light sheets.
So to generate an MP3
or an m4a of this Twitter
space.
And then
what are we going to
do with
the transcript Rocky.
Because
you know cloud go back.
And I am I'm using
cursor for now.
I mean, you can try
running
a summary on your own,
but you should
send a copy to me
and then I'll run it
through sonnet for 4.1.
Right.
And see if it's better.
Maybe if it's something
that the cursor doesn't.
That's a great idea. So,
I guess I should do
the summary.
This is being,
the organized media
featuring
the syndicate stacks
AI guild applied AGI.
AGI is, as AGI
does, unanimous
AI has proven
through their predictions
of the Oscars and the NC
Double-A Final Four
and the MLB winners
that because they do
the best predictions
on the market
that they're
implementation of
AI is fiscally the most
rewarding of all
implementations of AI.
And they are specifically
including humans in
the loop
to make the
best bets on the planet.
So if AGI is, as AGI does,
the real benefit of AI, in
my opinion,
is to increase
collaboration between
the humans together
such that the
AI can have
the information
that the AI doesn't
necessarily have
in documented shops
or on the internet,
the signals
that are only processed
by humans and their unique
gifts of bias.
Again, this is being
the syndicate
on the organized stacks
AI Guild.
We hope to see you soon.